so now that we have seen and those law
let's do a quiz let's say we have a
program with 50 billion instructions
that execute let's say that we have a
processor clocked at 2 gigahertz let's
say that we improve the branch
instructions so that it no longer takes
4 cycles to do one now it takes only 2
cycles to do 1 this is a table where we
show for each of the 4 instruction types
integer branches loads and stores the
percentage of all instructions in the
program that are of this type so for
example 40% of all instructions that we
execute our integer instructions 20% of
all instructions that we execute our
branch instructions 30% our loads and
10% our stores and finally we have the
CPI for each of these types of
instructions for integer it's 1 for
branches it was for the improvement
reduces that to two loads spend 2 cycles
per instruction and stores spend 3
cycles per instruction the question for
you is what is the overall speed of put
your answer here